





GAN Integrity

Bizzon / MEWS

mbit Studio / Showfall AB

VSITE

ABOUT ME

Started as a web developer in 2012, with a strong focus on the backend (LAMP stack) and occasionally frontend, being flexible to complete various tasks for different companies.

Since 2017, I've expanded my career in data integration and gained my path into system and network development with the continuous will to learn through books, local meetups, contributing open source projects, and international conferences.

EXPERIENCE

12/2023 - current Copenhagen, Denmark

Backend developer

Developed backend for scalable enterprise system.

Node / ELK / aws / CI / PostgreSQL / Koa / Typescript / MongoDB

Remote Position

7/2021 - 10/2023 Full-Stack developer

Developed backend and frontend for complex POS system.

GO / ELK / aws / CI / PostgreSQL / Rails / Typescript / React / Redux

11/2018 - 6/2021 Freelance

> Fixing, optimizing, adding new features for various web systems, using integration tests, implementing performance monitoring (as New Relic).

Provided up to 10x faster API response time, removed existing DB deadlocks.

Go / TypeScript / Ruby / Linux

3/2017 - 10/2018 Zagreb, Croatia

Big Data Integration developer

Provided data analyses, and data collection drivers for Media Companies such as SKY, Canal+,

Proximus, Freesat, T-Com.

Helped company to provide accurate television analytics for our clients.

Lua / C++ / Rust / nix / Linux

11/2013 - 2/2017

Zagreb, Croatia

Full stack developer

Developed payment solution, seating policy, geolocation train tracking (with websockets) for MTR

Express (Sweden).

As a lead back-end developer on MTR Express project, was among those who brought the largest

revenue to the company.

PHP / Python / GO / PostgreSQL / Couchbase / Redis / Linux / Nginx

4/2013 - 10/2013

Zagreb, Croatia

Junior Backend Developer

Trikoder Junior backend (PHP) maintainer for web system such as wogibtswas, rbainvest, ichkoche.

PHP / MySQL / JS / CMS / Linux / Apache

EDUCATION

2012 - 2019 Part-time student

Bachelor's Degree

Visoka škola za informacijske tehnologije, Zagreb

Computing science

LANGUAGES

Croatian - native English - proficient **German** - rudimentary

Danish - Level 2

PRESENTATIONS

WASM <3 Rust - Zagreb Rust Meetup, May 2^{nd} 2019

Rust FFI and Web Assembly -Seoul 서울 Rust Meetup, Sep 24^{th} 2019

CONTRIBUTIONS

bpftrace - High-level tracing language for Linux eBPF

Photon High-performance image processing library - Rust+WASM Zemeroth Turn-based tactical

game - Rust+WASM